<Database>
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ONCOLOGYSL_DIAGNOSES">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
		
        <!-- Diagnoses - Skin Cancer -->
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 1, the tumour is roughly 2 centimeters wide or smaller and may have spread into the dermis.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 2, the tumour is larger than 2 centimeters wide, may have spread into the dermis and has high risk features such as perineural invasion.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 3, the cancer has spread to areas below the skin, such as into muscle, bone, cartilage, or lymph nodes, but only those near the original tumor.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 4, the cancer has spread to areas outside the skin, such as to distant organs like the brain or lungs, or has invaded the skeleton.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 1, the tumour is roughly 2 centimeters wide or smaller and may have spread into the dermis.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 2, the tumour is larger than 2 centimeters wide, may have spread into the dermis and has high risk features such as perineural invasion.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 3, the cancer has spread to areas below the skin, such as into muscle, bone, cartilage, or lymph nodes, but only those near the original tumor.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 4, the cancer has spread to areas outside the skin, such as to distant organs like the brain or lungs, or has invaded the skeleton.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nIn Stage 1, the Cancer has spread deeper into the skin but has not spread to lymph nodes or other parts of the body.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 2 melanoma is thicker, extending through the epidermis and further into the dermis, the dense inner layer of the skin. It has a higher chance of spreading.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 3 describes melanoma that has spread locally or through the lymphatic system to a regional lymph node. It has not spread to distant lymph nodes or organs though.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 4 describes melanoma that has spread through the bloodstream to other parts of the body, such as distant locations on the skin or soft tissue, distant lymph nodes, or other organs.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- Diagnoses - Adrenal Gland Cancer -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumor of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Localised, the tumor is detected at an early stage in the adrenal medulla in one or both adrenal glands.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumor of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Regional, the cancer has spread from where the tumor began to nearby surrounding tissues and/or lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumor of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Metastatic, the cancer has spread from where the tumor began to a distant part of the body.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- Diagnoses - Lung Cancer -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>NSC Lung Cancer (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumor, a lesion, or a nodule. A lung tumor can begin anywhere in the lung. Localised, the cancer is found in the lung but has not progressed to the lymph nodes or distant organs.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>NSC Lung Cancer (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumor, a lesion, or a nodule. A lung tumor can begin anywhere in the lung. Regional, the cancer has progressed from the lungs to nearby lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>NSC Lung Cancer (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumor, a lesion, or a nodule. A lung tumor can begin anywhere in the lung. Metastatic, the cancer has progressed from the lungs to nearby lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>SC Lung Cancer (Limited Stage)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>SCLC begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumor, a lesion, or a nodule. SCLC begins in the nerve cells or hormone-producing cells of the lung. The term “small cell” refers to the size and shape of the cancer cells as seen under a microscope. Limited stage means that the cancer is only in 1 part of the chest and radiation therapy could be a treatment option. About 1 out of 3 people with SCLC have limited stage disease when first diagnosed.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>SC Lung Cancer (Extensive Stage)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>SCLC begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumor, a lesion, or a nodule. SCLC begins in the nerve cells or hormone-producing cells of the lung. The term “small cell” refers to the size and shape of the cancer cells as seen under a microscope. Extensive stage is used to describe SCLC that has spread to parts of the body such as the other lung, bone, brain, or bone marrow. Many doctors consider SCLC that has spread to the fluid around the lung to be extensive stage as well. About 2 out of 3 people with SCLC have extensive disease when the cancer is first found.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Colorectal Adenocarcinoma (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum make up 95 percent of all colorectal cancer cases. In the gastrointestinal tract, rectal and colon adenocarcinomas develop in the cells of the lining inside the large intestine. Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum typically start as a growth of tissue called a polyp. A particular type of polyp called an adenoma may develop into cancer. Localised, the cancer is confined to the bowel wall or may have spread to the outer surface of the bowel wall.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Colorectal Adenocarcinoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum make up 95 percent of all colorectal cancer cases. In the gastrointestinal tract, rectal and colon adenocarcinomas develop in the cells of the lining inside the large intestine. Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum typically start as a growth of tissue called a polyp. A particular type of polyp called an adenoma may develop into cancer. Regional, the cancer has spread in lymph nodes near the bowel.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Colorectal Adenocarcinoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum make up 95 percent of all colorectal cancer cases. In the gastrointestinal tract, rectal and colon adenocarcinomas develop in the cells of the lining inside the large intestine. Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum typically start as a growth of tissue called a polyp. A particular type of polyp called an adenoma may develop into cancer. Metastatic, the cancer is found at distant sites and has spread.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>

