<Database>
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ONCOLOGYSL_TREATMENTS">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_IMIQUIMOD_CREAM</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Imiquimod Cream</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_IMIQUIMOD_CREAM_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Imiquimod is a prescription cream that acts as an immune response modifier that is used to treat superficial basal cell carcinoma and actinic keratosi.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_PHOTODYNAMIC_THERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Photodynamic Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_PHOTODYNAMIC_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Photodynamic therapy is a treatment that uses certain drugs called photosensitizing agents, along with a special light, to kill cancer cells.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_MOHS_MICROGRAPHIC_SURGERY</LocID>                               
	<Text>Mohs Micrographic Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_MOHS_MICROGRAPHIC_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                   
	<Text>Mohs surgery is an advanced surgical technique that precisely removes all forms of skin cancer while preserving healthy surrounding tissue.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SL_DOCTORS_ADVICE</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Oncology Patient Advice</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SL_DOCTORS_ADVICE_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>The doctor gives the patient advice on how to deal with their situation, helps the patient better understand their options such as palliative care and does whatever they can to ensure the patient has the best quality of life possible during this time.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_TARGETED_THERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Targeted Therapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_TARGETED_THERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Targeted therapy works by targeting the cancer's specific genes, proteins, or the tissue environment that contributes to cancer growth and survival.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_CHEMOTHERAPY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Chemotherapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_CHEMOTHERAPY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Chemotherapy is a type of cancer treatment that uses one or more anti-cancer drugs as part of a standardized chemotherapy regimen. Chemotherapy may be given with a curative intent, or it may aim to prolong life or to reduce symptoms.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_LAPAROSCOPIC_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Laparoscopic Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_LAPAROSCOPIC_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Laparoscopic or “minimally invasive” surgery is a specialized technique for performing surgery. It's a low-risk, minimally invasive procedure that requires only small incisions. Laparoscopy uses an instrument called a laparoscope to look at the abdominal organs.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_LOBECTOMY_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Pulmonary Lobectomy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_LOBECTOMY_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Pulmonary Lobectomy of the lung is a surgical operation where a lobe of the lung is removed. It is done to remove a portion of diseased lung, such as early stage lung cancer.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_ENDOVASCULAR_EMBOLISATION</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Endovascular Embolization</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_ENDOVASCULAR_EMBOLISATION_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Endovascular embolization (EE) is an invasive surgical procedure. It’s used to treat abnormal blood vessels found in your brain, as well as other areas of your body. This procedure is an alternative to open surgery. It blocks blood vessels to cut off blood flow to an affected area.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_IMMUNOTHERAPY_DRUGS</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Immunotherapy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_IMMUNOTHERAPY_DRUGS_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Immunotherapy is a type of cancer treatment which assists the body's immune system to fight cancer.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_NERVE_DECOM_SURGERY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Nerve Reconstructive Surgery</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_NERVE_DECOM_SURGERY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>Surgical nerve repair involves exploration of the injured nerve and removal of injured tissue or scar from the nerve endings. After that, a nerve can be directly reconnected if there is enough length on the ends to allow for a good quality repair without tension.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_EPIPEN</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Epinephrine Autoinjector</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_EPIPEN_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>An epinephrine autoinjector is a medical device for injecting a measured dose or doses of epinephrine by means of autoinjector technology. It is most often used for the treatment of anaphylaxis.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_POLYPECTOMY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Polypectomy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_POLYPECTOMY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>A polypectomy is a procedure used to remove polyps from the inside of the colon, also called the large intestine. A polyp is an abnormal collection of tissue. The procedure is relatively noninvasive.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_PARTIAL_COLECTOMY</LocID>                                    	
	<Text>Colectomy</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>

	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
	<LocID>TRT_SLP_PARTIAL_COLECTOMY_DESC</LocID>                        	
	<Text>A Colectomy is bowel resection of the large bowel. It consists of the surgical removal of any extent of the colon, usually segmental resection. In extreme cases where the entire large intestine is removed.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>
