<Database>
	<!-- Oncology Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ONCOLOGYSL_DIAGNOSESOLD">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
		
        <!-- Diagnoses - Skin Cancer -->
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 1, the tumour is roughly 2 centimeters wide or smaller and may have spread into the dermis.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 2, the tumour is larger than 2 centimeters wide, may have spread into the dermis and has high risk features such as perineural invasion.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 3, the cancer has spread to areas below the skin, such as into muscle, bone, cartilage, or lymph nodes, but only those near the original tumour.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Basal Cell Carcinoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC1_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Basal cell cancer is the most common form of cancer in humans. It is a type of non-melanoma skin cancer that starts in the basal cell layer of the epidermis (the top layer of skin), grows very slowly, and rarely spreads (metastasizes).\n\nIn Stage 4, the cancer has spread to areas outside the skin, such as to distant organs like the brain or lungs, or has invaded the skeleton.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 1, the tumour is roughly 2 centimeters wide or smaller and may have spread into the dermis.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 2, the tumour is larger than 2 centimeters wide, may have spread into the dermis and has high risk features such as perineural invasion.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 3, the cancer has spread to areas below the skin, such as into muscle, bone, cartilage, or lymph nodes, but only those near the original tumour.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Carcinoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC2_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the skin is a common form of skin cancer that develops in the squamous cells that make up the middle and outer layers of the skin.\n\nIn Stage 4, the cancer has spread to areas outside the skin, such as to distant organs like the brain or lungs, or has invaded the skeleton.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nIn Stage 1, the Cancer has spread deeper into the skin but has not spread to lymph nodes or other parts of the body.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 2 melanoma is thicker, extending through the epidermis and further into the dermis, the dense inner layer of the skin. It has a higher chance of spreading.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 3 describes melanoma that has spread locally or through the lymphatic system to a regional lymph node. It has not spread to distant lymph nodes or organs though.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_4</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_4_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Melanoma occurs when pigment cells in the skin (called melanocytes) mutate and begin growing out of control.\n\nStage 4 describes melanoma that has spread through the bloodstream to other parts of the body, such as distant locations on the skin or soft tissue, distant lymph nodes, or other organs.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- Diagnoses - Adrenal Gland Cancer -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumour of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Localised, the tumour is detected at an early stage in the adrenal medulla in one or both adrenal glands.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumour of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Regional, the cancer has spread from where the tumour began to nearby surrounding tissues and/or lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pheochromocytoma is a rare tumour of adrenal gland tissue. It results in the release of too much epinephrine and norepinephrine, hormones that control heart rate, metabolism, and blood pressure. Metastatic, the cancer has spread from where the tumour began to a distant part of the body. To predict the likelihood of metastatic spread, several criteria and scoring systems have been developed on the basis of histopathology or clinical data, but no system has proven reliable.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- Diagnoses - Lung Cancer -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>UD NSC Lung Cancer (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Undifferentiated Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumour, a lesion, or a nodule. A lung tumour can begin anywhere in the lung. Undifferentiated is used to describe cells or tissues that do not have specialized ("mature") structures or functions. Undifferentiated cancer cells often grow and spread quickly. Localised, the cancer is found in the lung but has not progressed to the lymph nodes or distant organs.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>UD NSC Lung Cancer (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Undifferentiated Non-Small Cell Lung Cancer (NSCLC) begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumour, a lesion, or a nodule. A lung tumour can begin anywhere in the lung. Undifferentiated is used to describe cells or tissues that do not have specialized ("mature") structures or functions. Undifferentiated cancer cells often grow and spread quickly. Regional, the cancer has progressed from the lungs to nearby lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Lung Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Lung cancer begins when abnormal cells grow and multiply in an uncontrolled way in one or both of the lungs. It can spread to other parts of the body such as the lymph nodes, brain, adrenal glands, liver and bones. When a tumour grows and becomes more aggressive, it requires more space and begins to spread to other areas. This stage is the start of metastatic lung cancer.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>SC Lung Cancer (Limited Stage)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Small Cell Lung Cancer begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumour, a lesion, or a nodule. SCLC begins in the nerve cells or hormone-producing cells of the lung. The term “small cell” refers to the size and shape of the cancer cells as seen under a microscope. Limited stage means that the cancer is only in 1 part of the chest and radiation therapy could be a treatment option. About 1 out of 3 people with SCLC have limited stage disease when first diagnosed.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>SC Lung Cancer (Extensive Stage)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Small Cell Lung Cancer begins when healthy cells in the lung change and grow out of control, forming a mass called a tumour, a lesion, or a nodule. SCLC begins in the nerve cells or hormone-producing cells of the lung. The term “small cell” refers to the size and shape of the cancer cells as seen under a microscope. Extensive stage is used to describe SCLC that has spread to parts of the body such as the other lung, bone, brain, or bone marrow. Many doctors consider SCLC that has spread to the fluid around the lung to be extensive stage as well. About 2 out of 3 people with SCLC have extensive disease when the cancer is first found.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Colorectal Adenocarcinoma (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum make up 95 percent of all colorectal cancer cases. In the gastrointestinal tract, rectal and colon adenocarcinomas develop in the cells of the lining inside the large intestine. Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum typically start as a growth of tissue called a polyp. A particular type of polyp called an adenoma may develop into cancer. Localised, the cancer is confined to the bowel wall or may have spread to the outer surface of the bowel wall.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Colorectal Adenocarcinoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum make up 95 percent of all colorectal cancer cases. In the gastrointestinal tract, rectal and colon adenocarcinomas develop in the cells of the lining inside the large intestine. Adenocarcinomas of the colon and rectum typically start as a growth of tissue called a polyp. A particular type of polyp called an adenoma may develop into cancer. Regional, the cancer has spread in lymph nodes near the bowel.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Colorectal Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>If the cancer in the bowel is not detected and removed at an early stage, part of the tumour can break off from the main bowel tumour and spread, usually via the lymphatic system or bloodstream, to nearby lymph nodes or other parts of the body. If the cancer has spread to another part of the body (for example, the liver or lungs) it is called metastatic cancer or secondary (advanced) cancer.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Adrenocortical Carcinoma (Localised)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adrenocortical carcinoma is a rare disease in which malignant (cancer) cells form in the outer layer of the adrenal gland. Localised, the tumour is 5 centimeters or smaller and is found in the adrenal gland only.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Adrenocortical Carcinoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adrenocortical carcinoma is a rare disease in which malignant (cancer) cells form in the outer layer of the adrenal gland. Regional, the tumour is any size and has spread to nearby lymph nodes or nearby tissues or organs (kidney, diaphragm, pancreas, spleen, or liver) or to large blood vessels (renal vein or vena cava) and may have spread to nearby lymph nodes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Adrenocortical Carcinoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_AGC2_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adrenocortical carcinoma is a rare disease in which malignant (cancer) cells form in the outer layer of the adrenal gland. Metastatic, the tumour is any size, may have spread to nearby lymph nodes, and has spread to other parts of the body, such as the lung, bone, or peritoneum.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_MC001_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Gastrointestinal NET (LS)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_MC001_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Neuroendocrine Tumours(NETs) are neoplasms that arise from cells of the endocrine (hormonal) and nervous systems. Many are benign, while some are malignant. They most commonly occur in the intestine, where they are often called carcinoid tumours, but they are also found in the pancreas, lung and the rest of the body. Limited Stage, the tumour is smaller than 4 cm and has grown as far as the membrane that connects the appendix to the abdomen wall.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_MC001_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Gastrointestinal NET (ES)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_MC001_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Neuroendocrine Tumours (NETs) are neoplasms that arise from cells of the endocrine (hormonal) and nervous systems. Many are benign, while some are malignant. They most commonly occur in the intestine, where they are often called carcinoid tumours, but they are also found in the pancreas, lung and the rest of the body. Extensive Stage, the tumour has grown through the peritoneum or has invaded nearby organs or structures.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (Pre-B Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Pre-B Cell Acute lymphocytic Leukaemia (ALL) (Also known as Acute lymphoblastic leukaemia) is a type of cancer that affects the blood and bone marrow. ALL is characterised by an overproduction of immature white blood cells, called lymphoblasts or leukaemic blasts. Because the bone marrow is unable to make adequate numbers of red cells, normal white cells and platelets, people with ALL become more susceptible to anaemia, recurrent infections, and to bruising and bleeding easily. In between 75-80% of adult cases, ALL arises in B-lymphocytes in the early stages of development in the bone marrow. The disease is therefore called precursor B-cell ALL or Pre-B-cell ALL.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (B Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>B-cell Acute Lymphocytic Leukaemia, also known as Burkitt-type acute lymphoblastic leukaemia (B-ALL) or Mature B-cell acute lymphoblastic leukaemia (ALL) is a cancer that affects your "B lymphocytes" -- white blood cells that grow in the soft center of your bones, called marrow. This type of ALL is less common accounting for around 3-5% of all adult cases. The hallmark of mature B-cell ALL is the presence of surface immunoglobulin on the lymphoblasts. Using conventional regimens, only 30-40% of patients enter complete remission (CR) and few patients survive long term.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (T Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>T-cell Acute Lymphocytic Leukaemia (T-ALL) is a type of acute leukaemia meaning that it is aggressive and progresses quickly. It affects the lymphoid-cell-producing stem cells, in paticular a type of white blood cell called T lymphocytes as opposed to acute lymphoblastic leukaemia (ALL) which commonly affects B lymphocytes.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_A</LocID>                         
		<Text>CLL (Stable)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_A_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Chronic Lymphocytic Leukaemia (CLL)(Stable) is a type of slow-growing leukaemia that affects developing B-lymphocytes. B lymphocytes (also known as B-cells) are specialised white blood cells. Under normal conditions they produce immunoglobulins (also called antibodies) that help protect our bodies against infection and disease. In people with CLL, lymphocytes undergo a malignant (cancerous) change and become leukaemic cells. It is important to emphasise that for many people CLL remains stable for many months and years and has little, if any, impact on their lifestyle or general health. Around 30-50% of people diagnosed with CLL never require any treatment for their disease and can survive for many years despite their diagnosis. Because CLL develops slowly many people don’t have any symptoms, particularly in the early stages, and the disease is picked up during a routine blood test.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_B</LocID>                         
		<Text>CLL (Advanced)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_B_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Chronic Lymphocytic Leukaemia (CLL)(Advanced)(Rare) is a type of slow-growing leukaemia that affects developing B-lymphocytes. B lymphocytes (also known as B-cells) are specialised white blood cells. Under normal conditions they produce immunoglobulins (also called antibodies) that help protect our bodies against infection and disease. In people with CLL, lymphocytes undergo a malignant (cancerous) change and become leukaemic cells. It is important to emphasise that for many people CLL remains stable for many months and years and has little, if any, impact on their lifestyle or general health. Around 30-50% of people diagnosed with CLL never require any treatment for their disease and can survive for many years despite their diagnosis. Because CLL develops slowly many people don’t have any symptoms, particularly in the early stages, and the disease is picked up during a routine blood test.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>T-cell LGL Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>T-Cell large granular lymphocytic (LGL) leukaemia is a type of chronic leukaemia affecting white blood cells called "lymphocytes." Lymphocytes are part of the body's immune system and help fight certain infections. LGL leukemia is characterized by enlarged lymphocytes, containing noticeable granules, which can be seen when the blood is examined under the microscope. There are two types of LGL leukemia: T-cell (T-LGL) and natural killer cell (NK-LGL). The frequency of T-cell and NK-cell LGL leukaemia ranges from 2 to 5 percent. T-cell large granular lymphocyte (LGL) leukaemia is a clonal proliferation of cytotoxic T cells, which causes neutropenia, anemia, and/or thrombocytopenia. This condition is often associated with autoimmune disorders, especially rheumatoid arthritis, and other lymphoproliferative disorders.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>NK-cell LGL Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>NK-Cell large granular lymphocytic (LGL) leukaemia is a type of chronic leukaemia affecting white blood cells called "lymphocytes." Lymphocytes are part of the body's immune system and help fight certain infections. LGL leukemia is characterized by enlarged lymphocytes, containing noticeable granules, which can be seen when the blood is examined under the microscope. There are two types of LGL leukemia: T-cell (T-LGL) and natural killer cell (NK-LGL). The frequency of T-cell and NK-cell LGL leukaemia ranges from 2 to 5 percent. The majority of patients with NK-cell leukaemia are asymptomatic, but patients with an aggressive variant usually have hepatomegaly and splenomegaly and often have B symptoms. About a third have lymphadenopathy and extranodal involvement may also occur. On average, patients are younger than those with T-cell LGL leukaemia.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>T-cell Prolymphocytic Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>T-cell prolymphocytic leukaemia (T-PLL) is an extremely rare and typically aggressive malignancy (cancer) that is characterized by the out of control growth of mature T-cells (T-lymphocytes). T-cells are a type of white blood cell that protects the body from infections. T-PLL affects older adults with a median age at diagnosis of 61 years, and it is more common in men than in women. Abnormal changes (mutations) in the genes of a T-cell can cause a normal, healthy T-cell to become a cancer cell. These genetic errors in the mutated T-cell tell the cell to keep growing and dividing when a healthy cell would typically stop dividing and eventually die. Every cell that arises from the initial leukemia cell also has the same mutated DNA. As a result, over time the number of leukaemia cells multiply and can travel in the blood to other sites including the bone marrow, spleen, liver, lymph nodes and sometimes skin.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC04_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Acute Myeloid Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC04_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Acute Myeloid Leukaemia develops when the body makes too many immature white blood cells known as myeloid blast cells, also called myeloblasts. The myeloblasts multiply out of control and continue to divide but never mature into normal cells.  The abnormal blast cells are known as leukaemia cells. Because the leukaemia cells are immature and abnormal, they don’t carry out the usual infection-fighting function of white blood cells. They also crowd out normal white blood cells, which then can’t work properly. This increases the risk of infections.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_A</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Chronic Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_A_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Chronic Myeloid Leukaemia (CML)(Chronic Phase) is a type of cancer that affects the blood and bone marrow. In CML the bone marrow produces too many white cells, called granulocytes. These cells (sometimes called blasts or leukaemic blasts) gradually crowd the bone marrow, interfering with normal blood cell production. They also spill out of the bone marrow and circulate around the body in the bloodstream. Because they are not fully mature, they are unable to work properly to fight infections. Over time, a shortage of red cells and platelets can cause anaemia, bleeding and/or bruising. Overall, CML is a rare disease, accounting for around 0.03% of all cancers diagnosed. Many people with chronic myeloid leukaemia (CML) have no symptoms. Chronic – The white blood cell count is increased and a small number of immature cells called blast cells are found in the blood and bone marrow.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_B</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Accelerated  Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_B_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Chronic Myeloid Leukaemia (CML)(Accelerated  Phase) is a type of cancer that affects the blood and bone marrow. In CML the bone marrow produces too many white cells, called granulocytes. These cells (sometimes called blasts or leukaemic blasts) gradually crowd the bone marrow, interfering with normal blood cell production. They also spill out of the bone marrow and circulate around the body in the bloodstream. Because they are not fully mature, they are unable to work properly to fight infections. Over time, a shortage of red cells and platelets can cause anaemia, bleeding and/or bruising. Overall, CML is a rare disease, accounting for around 0.03% of all cancers diagnosed. Many people with chronic myeloid leukaemia (CML) have no symptoms. Accelerated – In the accelerated phase, the number of immature blast cells has risen, and sometimes new chromosomal changes, in addition to the Ph chromosome, will occur.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_C</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Blast Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_C_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Chronic Myeloid Leukaemia (CML)(Blast Phase) is a type of cancer that affects the blood and bone marrow. In CML the bone marrow produces too many white cells, called granulocytes. These cells (sometimes called blasts or leukaemic blasts) gradually crowd the bone marrow, interfering with normal blood cell production. They also spill out of the bone marrow and circulate around the body in the bloodstream. Because they are not fully mature, they are unable to work properly to fight infections. Over time, a shortage of red cells and platelets can cause anaemia, bleeding and/or bruising. Overall, CML is a rare disease, accounting for around 0.03% of all cancers diagnosed. Many people with chronic myeloid leukaemia (CML) have no symptoms. Blast Crisis – Blast Phase (Also Called "Blast Crisis Phase"). The blast phase appears and behaves like the acute form of myeloid leukemia.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC06_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Hairy Cell Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC06_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Hairy cell leukaemia (HCL) is a rare type of chronic leukaemia of the lymphoid system, in which abnormal B-lymphocytes accumulate in the bone marrow, liver and spleen. Under the microscope, these cells are seen to have tiny hair-like projections on their surface, hence their name “hairy cell”.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC06_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Hairy Cell Leukaemia Variant</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC06_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Hairy Cell Leukemia variant (HCL-V) is defined as a rare and indolent form of small, mature, B-cell leukemia characterized by splenomegaly, an elevated white blood cell (WBC) count and hyper-cellular bone marrow. HCL-V is more aggressive and resistant to therapy than classical HCL. HCL variant was previously thought to be a subtype of HCL, but in 2008, the World Health Organization concluded that it was a separate entity from HCL and biologically distinct. HCL variant is rarer than HCL and has a different clinical course.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- ### ### -->
		<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13 Added Below ######################################## -->
		<!-- ### ### -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Ductal Carcinoma In Situ</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_0M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Ductal Carcinoma In Situ</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Ductal carcinoma in situ (DCIS) is non-invasive breast cancer.  Ductal means that the cancer starts inside the milk ducts, carcinoma refers to any cancer that begins in the skin or other tissues (including breast tissue) that cover or line the internal organs, and in situ means "in its original place." DCIS is called "non-invasive" because it hasn’t spread beyond the milk duct into any normal surrounding breast tissue. DCIS isn’t life-threatening, but having DCIS can increase the risk of developing an invasive breast cancer later on. Ductal carcinoma in situ (DCIS) means that there are too many cells and they have the features of cancer, but they are still confined to the inside of the duct. Although it is rare, men can develop breast cancer. \n\nDCIS generally has no signs or symptoms.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Invasive Ductal Carcinoma (IDC)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_1M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Invasive Ductal Carcinoma (IDC)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Invasive ductal carcinoma (IDC), sometimes called infiltrating ductal carcinoma, is the most common type of breast cancer. About 80% of all breast cancers are invasive ductal carcinomas. Invasive means that the cancer has “invaded” or spread to the surrounding breast tissues. Ductal means that the cancer began in the milk ducts, which are the “pipes” that carry milk from the milk-producing lobules to the nipple. Carcinoma refers to any cancer that begins in the skin or other tissues that cover internal organs — such as breast tissue. All together, “invasive ductal carcinoma” refers to cancer that has broken through the wall of the milk duct and begun to invade the tissues of the breast. Over time, invasive ductal carcinoma can spread to the lymph nodes and possibly to other areas of the body. Although it is rare, men can develop breast cancer. \n\nAt first, invasive ductal carcinoma may not cause any symptoms.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Breast Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_2M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Breast Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Metastatic breast cancer (also called stage IV) is breast cancer that has spread to another part of the body, most commonly the liver, brain, bones, or lungs. Cancer cells can break away from the original tumour in the breast and travel to other parts of the body through the bloodstream or the lymphatic system, which is a large network of nodes and vessels that works to remove bacteria, viruses, and cellular waste products. Breast cancer can come back in another part of the body months or years after the original diagnosis and treatment. Nearly 30% of women diagnosed with early-stage breast cancer will develop metastatic disease. Although it is rare, men can develop breast cancer.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pilocytic Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Grade I astrocytomas are also called pilocytic astrocytomas. These tumours occur in children and young adults. They are less invasive than other grades and have a relatively good prognosis.  They usually arise in the cerebellum, near the brainstem, in the hypothalamic region, or the optic chiasm, but they may occur in any area where astrocytes are present, including the cerebral hemispheres and the spinal cord. These tumours are usually slow growing and benign.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Diffuse Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Diffuse astrocytomas, also referred to as low-grade infiltrative astrocytomas, are designated as WHO II tumours of the brain. The term diffuse infiltrating means there is no identifiable border between the tumour and normal brain tissue, even though the borders may appear well-marginated on imaging.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Anaplastic Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Anaplastic astrocytoma is a rare malignant brain tumour. Astrocytomas are tumours that develop from certain star-shaped brain cells called astrocytes. Astrocytes and similar cells form tissue that surrounds and protects other nerve cells found within the brain and spinal cord.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Glioblastoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BRAC1_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Glioblastoma, also known as glioblastoma multiforme (GBM), is the most aggressive cancer that begins within the brain. Initially, signs and symptoms of glioblastoma are nonspecific. They may include headaches, personality changes, nausea, and symptoms similar to those of a stroke.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_0F</LocID>                         
		<Text>High-Grade Serous Carcinoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_0F_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>High-Grade serous ovarian carcinoma (HGSC) is a type of tumour that arises from the serous epithelial layer in the abdominopelvic cavity and is mainly found in the ovary. HGSCs make up the majority of ovarian cancer cases[1] and have the lowest survival rates. HGSC is distinct from low-grade serous carcinoma (LGSC) which arises from ovarian tissue and is less aggressive.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_1F</LocID>                         
		<Text>Low-Grade Serous Carcinoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_1F_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Low-grade serous ovarian cancer is a rare disease, accounting for  less than 10% of ovarian cancer cases. Low-grade serous carcinoma of the ovary (LGSC) is less common and aggressive than high-grade types of ovarian cancer, but it resists many kinds of chemotherapy.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_2F</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Ovarian Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_OVAC1_2F_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Metastatic ovarian cancer is an advanced stage malignancy that has spread from the cells in the ovaries to distant areas of the body. This type of cancer is most likely to spread to the liver, the fluid around the lungs, the spleen, the intestines, the brain, skin or lymph nodes outside of the abdomen.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_0M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Prostate Cancer (Stage 1)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_0M_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Prostate cancer is cancer that occurs in the prostate, a small walnut-shaped gland in men that produces the seminal fluid that nourishes and transports sperm. Prostate cancer is one of the most common types of cancer in men. Usually prostate cancer grows slowly and is initially confined to the prostate gland, where it may not cause serious harm. However, while some types of prostate cancer grow slowly and may need minimal or even no treatment, other types are aggressive and can spread quickly. \n\nIn Stage 1, the cancer is confined to the prostate. Stage 1 can’t be detected during a digital rectal exam. It is usually expected to be slow growing.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_1M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Prostate Cancer (Stage 2)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_1M_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Prostate cancer is cancer that occurs in the prostate, a small walnut-shaped gland in men that produces the seminal fluid that nourishes and transports sperm. Prostate cancer is one of the most common types of cancer in men. Usually prostate cancer grows slowly and is initially confined to the prostate gland, where it may not cause serious harm. However, while some types of prostate cancer grow slowly and may need minimal or even no treatment, other types are aggressive and can spread quickly. \n\nWith Stage 2, cancer may be detected during a digital rectal exam. The disease is still confined to the prostate, but the cells may be abnormal and may grow faster.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_2M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Prostate Cancer (Stage 3)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_2M_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Prostate cancer is cancer that occurs in the prostate, a small walnut-shaped gland in men that produces the seminal fluid that nourishes and transports sperm. Prostate cancer is one of the most common types of cancer in men. Usually prostate cancer grows slowly and is initially confined to the prostate gland, where it may not cause serious harm. However, while some types of prostate cancer grow slowly and may need minimal or even no treatment, other types are aggressive and can spread quickly. \n\nWith Stage 3 prostate cancer, the cancer is in tissues near the prostate. It also may have reached the seminal vesicles.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_3M</LocID>                         
		<Text>Prostate Cancer (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_PROC1_3M_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Prostate cancer is cancer that occurs in the prostate, a small walnut-shaped gland in men that produces the seminal fluid that nourishes and transports sperm. Prostate cancer is one of the most common types of cancer in men. Usually prostate cancer grows slowly and is initially confined to the prostate gland, where it may not cause serious harm. However, while some types of prostate cancer grow slowly and may need minimal or even no treatment, other types are aggressive and can spread quickly. \n\nStage 4 prostate cancer means that cancer has invaded other parts of the body, such as the rectum, nearby lymph nodes or bone.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC07_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Diffuse Large B-Cell (NOS) Lymphoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC07_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Diffuse large B-cell lymphoma (Not Otherwise Specified)(DLBCL) is an aggressive type of non-Hodgkin lymphoma that develops from the B-cells in the lymphatic system. Under the microscope, large malignant lymphocytes are seen diffusely throughout the specimen. DLBCL is the most common subtype of non-Hodgkin lymphoma accounting for 30%-40% of all cases. There are several types of DLBCL, with most people being diagnosed with the subtype known as DLBCL ‘not otherwise specified’.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC08_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Follicular Lymphoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC08_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Follicular lymphoma is the most common sub-type of indolent (slow-growing) NHL (Non-Hodgkin Lymphoma), comprising 20% to 30% of all NHL. Follicular lymphoma typically affects middle-aged or older adult. Like most indolent lymphomas, people diagnosed with follicular lymphoma usually have lymphoma in many parts of the body at the time of diagnosis. A small percentage of people with FL can have their lymphoma transform into a more aggressive form of NHL, usually a DLBC over time. If diagnosed at an early stage there may be no treatment given (Watch and Wait).</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC4_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Merkel Cell Carcinoma (Local)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC4_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Merkel cell carcinoma (Rare) is a rare type of skin cancer that usually appears as a flesh-coloured or bluish-red nodule, often on your face, head or neck. Merkel cell carcinoma is also called neuroendocrine carcinoma of the skin. Merkel cell carcinoma tends to grow quickly and to metastasize (spread) at an early stage. It usually spreads first to nearby lymph nodes and then may spread to lymph nodes or skin in distant parts of the body, lungs, brain, bones, or other organs. Merkel cell carcinoma is the second most common cause of skin cancer death after melanoma.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC4_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Merkel Cell Carcinoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC4_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Merkel cell carcinoma (Rare) is a rare type of skin cancer that usually appears as a flesh-coloured or bluish-red nodule, often on your face, head or neck. Merkel cell carcinoma is also called neuroendocrine carcinoma of the skin. Merkel cell carcinoma tends to grow quickly and to metastasize (spread) at an early stage. It usually spreads first to nearby lymph nodes and then may spread to lymph nodes or skin in distant parts of the body, lungs, brain, bones, or other organs. Merkel cell carcinoma is the second most common cause of skin cancer death after melanoma.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- ### ### -->
		<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13.1a Added Below ######################################## -->
		<!-- ### ### -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC09_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mantle Cell Lymphoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC09_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Mantle cell lymphoma is a relatively uncommon type of lymphoma, accounting for approximately 5% to 10% of all non-Hodgkin lymphomas. It affects the outer edge (mantle zone) of B-cells in the lymph node follicle. In 85% of cases, an abnormality occurs when two chromosomes (11 and 14) break and join together with each other. This is called a ‘translocation’ and causes B-cells to over-produce a protein called cyclin D1. In usual quantities, Cyclin D1 helps to promote normal cell growth, with excess amounts resulting in uncontrolled growth of mantle zone cells which can lead to MCL.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- ### ### -->
		<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13.2.0 Added Below ######################################## -->
		<!-- ### ### -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC2_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Large Cell Lung Carcinoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC2_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Large cell carcinoma of the lungs is a form of non-small cell lung cancer. Non-small cell lung cancers account for 80 percent of lung cancers, and of these, roughly 10 percent are large cell carcinoma of the lung. ﻿Unlike some lung cancers that more commonly present with a cough or lung infections, early symptoms often include a vague sense of shortness of breath and fatigue. Large cell carcinomas are also called large cell lung cancers. They are named for the appearance of large round cells when examined under the microscope, although the tumours themselves tend to be large as well when diagnosed. Large cell carcinomas often occur in the outer regions of the lungs, and tend to grow rapidly and spread more quickly than some other forms of non-small cell lung cancer.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC3_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Lung Adenocarcinoma (Early)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC3_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinoma of the lung is the most common type of lung cancer, and like other forms of lung cancer, it is characterized by distinct cellular and molecular features. It is classified as one of several non-small cell lung cancers (NSCLC), to distinguish it from small cell lung cancer which has a different behavior and prognosis. Lung cancer typically doesn't cause signs and symptoms in its earliest stages. Signs and symptoms of lung cancer typically occur only when the disease is advanced. \n\nWith cancer that is detected early, the cancer is usually found only in the tissue or organ where it began, and has not spread to nearby lymph nodes or to other parts of the body.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC3_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Lung Adenocarcinoma (Advanced)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC3_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Adenocarcinoma of the lung is the most common type of lung cancer, and like other forms of lung cancer, it is characterized by distinct cellular and molecular features. It is classified as one of several non-small cell lung cancers (NSCLC), to distinguish it from small cell lung cancer which has a different behavior and prognosis. Lung cancer typically doesn't cause signs and symptoms in its earliest stages. Signs and symptoms of lung cancer typically occur only when the disease is advanced. \n\nWith advanced cancer, tumours can be of any size and have very likely spread to lymph nodes on the other side of the chest, near the collarbone, or have invaded other structures in the chest such as the heart or esophagus.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC4_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Squamous Cell Lung Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LC4_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Squamous cell carcinoma of the lungs, also called epidermoid carcinoma, is a type of non-small cell lung cancer that typically develops in one of the air passages, or bronchi, of the lungs. It is the second most common type of non-small cell lung cancer and accounts for roughly 30 percent of all lung cancer cases. This type of cancer is generally slow-growing, but it can eventually spread to other areas of the body.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC2_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Signet Ring Cell Colorectal Carcinoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC2_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Signet ring cell carcinoma (SRCC)(Rare) is a rare form of highly malignant adenocarcinoma that produces mucin. It is an epithelial malignancy characterized by the histologic appearance of signet ring cells. Primary SRCC tumours are most often found in the glandular cells of the stomach (SRCC originates in the stomach in 90 percent of patients), and less frequently in the breast, gallbladder, urinary bladder, and pancreas. SRCCs do not normally form in the lungs. Among colorectal cancers, the prevalence of SRCC is less than one percent.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC3_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucinous Colorectal Carcinoma (Mixed)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC3_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Mucinous colorectal carcinoma is a distinct subtype of colorectal cancer (CRC) characterized by the presence of abundant extracellular mucin which accounts for at least 50% of the tumour volume. Mucinous colorectal adenocarcinoma is found in 10%–20% of CRC patients. Mucinous carcinoma can form along side of other types cancer cells, when this happens, the cancer is referred to as mixed mucinous carcinoma.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC3_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucinous Colorectal Carcinoma (Prue)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BC3_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Mucinous colorectal carcinoma is a distinct subtype of colorectal cancer (CRC) characterized by the presence of abundant extracellular mucin which accounts for at least 50% of the tumour volume. Mucinous colorectal adenocarcinoma is found in 10%–20% of CRC patients. Mucinous carcinoma can form along side of other types cancer cells but when it doesn't the cancer is considered 'pure'.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- ### ### -->
		<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13.3.0 Added Below ######################################## -->
		<!-- ### ### -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_0</LocID>                         
		<Text>Hepatocellular Carcinoma (Local)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a primary malignancy of the liver that occurs predominantly in patients with underlying chronic liver disease and cirrhosis. However, up to 25% of patients have no history of cirrhosis or risk factors for it. Symptoms often don't appear in the early stages of the cancer.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Hepatocellular Carcinoma (Regional)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a primary malignancy of the liver that occurs predominantly in patients with underlying chronic liver disease and cirrhosis. However, up to 25% of patients have no history of cirrhosis or risk factors for it. Symptoms often don't appear in the early stages of the cancer. \n\nRegional, the cancer has progressed from the liver to nearby lymph nodes.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Hepatocellular Carcinoma (Critical)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Hepatocellular carcinoma (HCC) is a primary malignancy of the liver that occurs predominantly in patients with underlying chronic liver disease and cirrhosis. However, up to 25% of patients have no history of cirrhosis or risk factors for it. \n\nIn a critical state, spontaneous rupture of hepatocellular carcinoma(HCC) is a potentially life-threatening complication. Diagnosis may be difficult, particularly in the absence of known liver cirrhosis or tumour.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_3</LocID>                         
		<Text>Metastatic Liver Cancer</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_LIV0_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>A liver metastasis is a cancerous tumour that has spread to the liver from a cancer that started in another place in the body. It's also called secondary liver cancer. Primary liver cancer originates in the liver and most commonly affects individuals who have risk factors such as hepatitis or cirrhosis. When metastastic, it means that cancer has invaded other parts of the body, such as other organs, nearby lymph nodes or bone.</Text>
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<!-- ### ### -->
		<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13.4.0 Added Below ######################################## -->
		<!-- ### ### -->
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (Pre-B Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (B Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC01_2_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>ALL (T Cell)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_A_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>CLL (Stable)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC02_B_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>CLL (Advanced)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>T-cell LGL Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>NK-cell LGL Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC03_2_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>T-cell Prolymphocytic Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC04_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Acute Myeloid Leukaemia</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_A_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Chronic Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>

		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_B_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Accelerated  Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC05_C_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>CML (Blast Phase)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC08_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Follicular Lymphoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BLC07_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Diffuse Large B-Cell (NOS) Lymphoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Invasive Ductal Carcinoma (IDC)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_BREC1_1M_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Invasive Ductal Carcinoma (IDC)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_MC001_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Gastrointestinal NET (ES)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC3_4_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Melanoma (Stage 4)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_SC4_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Merkel Cell Carcinoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucoepidermoid Carcinoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_1_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Merkel Cell Carcinoma (Metastatic)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
	<!-- ### ### -->
	<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.13.4.1 Added Below ######################################## -->
	<!-- ### ### -->
	
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_1</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucoepidermoid Carcinoma (Low Grade)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_1_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucoepidermoid carcinomas are the most common type of salivary gland cancer. Most start in the parotid glands. They develop less often in the submandibular glands or in minor salivary glands inside the mouth. These cancers are usually low grade and a relatively less serious threat.  The major determinants of survival are histology and clinical stage. Poor prognostic factors include high grade, neural involvement, locally advanced disease, advanced age, associated pain, regional lymph node metastases, distant metastasis, and accumulation of p53 or c-erbB2 oncoproteins. Mucoepidermoid carcinoma can also be found in other organs, such as bronchi, lacrimal sac, and thyroid gland.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucoepidermoid Carcinoma (High Grade)</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_ORA001_2_DESC</LocID>                         
		<Text>Mucoepidermoid carcinomas are the most common type of salivary gland cancer. Most start in the parotid glands. They develop less often in the submandibular glands or in minor salivary glands inside the mouth. Approximately 80% of patients with facial nerve paralysis have nodal metastasis at the time of diagnosis. These patients have a much lower average survival rate compared to low grade tumours. The major determinants of survival are histology and clinical stage. Poor prognostic factors include high grade, neural involvement, locally advanced disease, advanced age, associated pain, regional lymph node metastases, distant metastasis, and accumulation of p53 or c-erbB2 oncoproteins.  Mucoepidermoid carcinoma can also be found in other organs, such as bronchi, lacrimal sac, and thyroid gland.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
	<!-- ### ### -->
	<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.14.0.2 Added Below ######################################## -->
	<!-- ### ### -->
		
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>

