<Database>
	<!-- Oncology Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ONCOLOGYSL_DIAGNOSES_NEURO">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_0_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Pilocytic Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_0_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Grade I astrocytomas are also called pilocytic astrocytomas. These tumours occur in children and young adults. They are less invasive than other grades and have a relatively good prognosis.  They usually arise in the cerebellum, near the brainstem, in the hypothalamic region, or the optic chiasm, but they may occur in any area where astrocytes are present, including the cerebral hemispheres and the spinal cord. These tumours are usually slow growing and benign.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_1_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Diffuse Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_1_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Diffuse astrocytomas, also referred to as low-grade infiltrative astrocytomas, are designated as WHO II tumours of the brain. The term diffuse infiltrating means there is no identifiable border between the tumour and normal brain tissue, even though the borders may appear well-marginated on imaging.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_2_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Anaplastic Astrocytoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_2_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Anaplastic astrocytoma is a rare malignant brain tumour. Astrocytomas are tumours that develop from certain star-shaped brain cells called astrocytes. Astrocytes and similar cells form tissue that surrounds and protects other nerve cells found within the brain and spinal cord.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
		<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_3_V2</LocID>                         
		<Text>Glioblastoma</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
		
        <GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>DIA_ONCO_CRP_BRAC1_3_DESC</LocID>             
		<Text>Glioblastoma, also known as glioblastoma multiforme (GBM), is the most aggressive cancer that begins within the brain. Initially, signs and symptoms of glioblastoma are nonspecific. They may include headaches, personality changes, nausea, and symptoms similar to those of a stroke.</Text>	
		</GameDBLocalizedString>
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>

