<Database>
	<!-- Oncology Mod by Sleepy068 -->
	<GameDBStringTable ID="LOC_EN_ADDON_ONCOLOGYSL_SYMPTOMS">
	<LanguageCode>en</LanguageCode>
	<LanguageNameLocalized>English</LanguageNameLocalized>
	<Contributors>
	<Name>Sleepy068</Name>
	</Contributors>

	<LocalizedStrings>
	<!-- ======================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Core Content ============= -->
	<!-- ======================================== -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_NERVE_DAMAGE</LocID>                               
		<Text>Postoperative Neuropathic Pain</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_NERVE_DAMAGE_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Postoperative neuropathic pain (PONP) can develop if nerves were damaged during a surgery. Damaged nerves cannot correctly transmit signals from various parts of the body to the brain. Instead, these signals become exaggerated, causing chronic pain that may persist for months or even years.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>    
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_LES_RUPTURE</LocID>                               
		<Text>Rupture of a Lesion</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>     
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_LES_RUPTURE_DESC</LocID>                               
		<Text>A lesion or tumour inside the patient has ruptured. This is associated with life-threatening internal bleeding.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_HEMOPTYSIS2</LocID>                               
		<Text>Severe Hemoptysis</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_HEMOPTYSIS2_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Hemoptysis is the coughing up of blood or blood-stained mucus from the bronchi, larynx, trachea, or lungs. In other words, it is the airway bleeding. This can occur with lung cancer, infections such as tuberculosis, bronchitis, or pneumonia, and certain cardiovascular conditions.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_SPLENOMEGALY</LocID>                               
		<Text>Splenomegaly</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_SPLENOMEGALY_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Splenomegaly is a condition that occurs when your spleen becomes enlarged. It’s also commonly referred to as enlarged spleen or spleen enlargement.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_RUP_SPLENOMEGALY</LocID>                               
		<Text>Ruptured Spleen</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_RUP_SPLENOMEGALY_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>A ruptured spleen is an emergency medical condition that occurs when the capsule-like covering of the spleen breaks open, pouring blood into your abdominal area. Depending on the size of the rupture, a large amount of internal bleeding can occur.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_HYPERCALCEMIA</LocID>                               
		<Text>Hypercalcemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_HYPERCALCEMIA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Hypercalcemia is a condition in which the calcium level in your blood is above normal. Hypercalcaemia is most often caused by overactivity in the four tiny glands in the neck (parathyroid glands) or from cancer. Extra calcium in the blood affects many bodily systems.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_SEVERE_HYPERCALCEMIA</LocID>                               
		<Text>Severe Hypercalcemia</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_SEVERE_HYPERCALCEMIA_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Severe hypercalcemia is a medical emergency requiring urgent treatment. Hypercalcemia is a condition in which the calcium level in your blood is above normal. Rarely, severe hypercalcemia can interfere with your heart function, causing palpitations and fainting, indications of cardiac arrhythmia, and other heart problems.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>    
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_ACUTE_LIVER_FAILURE</LocID>                               
		<Text>Acute Liver Failure</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>     
		<LocID>SYM_SLP_ACUTE_LIVER_FAILURE_DESC</LocID>                               
		<Text>Acute liver failure (ALF) is a rare syndrome defined by a rapid decline in hepatic function.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<!-- ### ### -->
	<!-- ######################################## Content for V0.15.0.0 Added Below ######################################## -->
	<!-- ### ### -->
	<!-- ======================================== -->
	<!-- ============= Core Content ============= -->
	<!-- ======================================== -->
	
	
	
	<!-- ============================================== -->
	<!-- ============= CRP Export Content ============= -->
	<!-- ============================================== -->
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BL_PMCC</LocID>                               
		<Text>Pure Mucinous Cells</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_BL_PMCC_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Mucinous carcinoma can form along side of other types cancer cells but when it doesn't the cancer is considered 'pure'. Pure mucinous carcinoma is composed of 90–100% mucinous cells.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CDF_T_25</LocID>                               
		<Text>p16INK4a Overexpression</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CDF_T_25_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>p16 (also known as p16INK4a, cyclin-dependent kinase inhibitor 2A, CDKN2A, multiple tumor suppressor 1 and numerous other synonyms), is a protein that slows cell division by slowing the progression of the cell cycle from the G1 phase to the S phase, thereby acting as a tumor suppressor. p16 is a widely used immunohistochemical marker in gynecologic pathology. Strong and diffuse cytoplasmic and nuclear expression of p16 in squamous cell carcinomas (SCC) of the female genital tract is strongly associated with high-risk human papilloma virus (HPV) infection and neoplasms of cervical origin. The majority of SCCs of uterine cervix express p16. However, p16 can be expressed in other neoplasms and in several normal human tissues.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CM_CK19_BRIGHT</LocID>                               
		<Text>Cytokeratin 19 (CK19) Brightly Expressed</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
            
	<GameDBLocalizedString>      
		<LocID>SYM_CRP_CM_CK19_BRIGHT_DESC</LocID>                   
		<Text>Keratin, type I cytoskeletal 19 also known as cytokeratin-19 (CK-19) or keratin-19 (K19) is a 40 kDa protein that in humans is encoded by the KRT19 gene. Expression in certain cancers allows CK19 to help act as a marker and help determine what type of cancer the patient may have.</Text>  
	</GameDBLocalizedString>
	
	</LocalizedStrings>
	</GameDBStringTable>
</Database>